1935 McLendon Ave NE Atlanta, Ga 30307 | 8034574113 | meghan.murphy@emory.edu

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Fourth year Bachelor of Science Emory student studying Anthropology/Human Biology, and will be graduating in December. Experienced, creative and reliable camp counselor who works well with children of all backgrounds. Hardworking, adaptable student athlete with excellent communication skills.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Supervising/leading children
Community engagement
Word, PowerPoint, Excel
Excellent teammate
(member of varsity softball and ultimate
frisbee teams at Emory University)
experience with organic farming

EXPERIENCE

10/2020-present

Community Outreach Coordinator, Atlanta Rescue Dog Cafe

 Acted as a liaison between the organization and various community groups such as schools and libraries, assisted with programming involving large groups of families, taught humane education and sustainability practices

9/2018-5/2019

Facility Attendant, Woodruff Physical Education Center

 Organized equipment rentals, communicated with guests regarding equipment rental and room availability, ensured safety of guests with knowledge of emergency and evacuation plans, kept and completed laundry schedule for many varsity teams

5/2018-8/2018

Education Coordinator, Zoo Atlanta

 Taught elementary-school children the importance of conservation and sustainable living, planned teaching activities based on a weekly theme, organized children through tours within the zoo, oversaw the health and safety of children in my group, worked with other coordinators to plan larger group activities, communicated with parents about children's wellbeing.

5/2017-8/2017

Summer Camp Counselor, Seven Oaks Park

Developed enrichment activities for the nine and ten-year-old children, settled
arguments between children, kept children entertained throughout the day with
activities they enjoyed, responsible for children's health and safety throughout the
day, worked with coworkers to share the space we had available

EDUCATION

8/2017-Present

BS Anthropology and Human Biology, Emory University, Atlanta, Ga